We We went through We went through a the
craziest time of our lives. We survived.
If you're here, you survived. And we did
things the last couple years we will
never do again.
I never forget when the pandemic hit, it
was right before Easter.
My pastor sent out an email cuz in
California they closed the churches. He
said, "We're doing Easter online."
And for communion, we're going to use
whatever you have at home.
I don't think I'll ever take again from
a NyQuil shot glass.
With prune juice and a flaming hot
Cheeto for the body of Christ.
>> We goof up some of our holidays, too.
Look at Easter.
What is Easter supposed to be about? The
resurrection of Christ. How'd the big
giant bunny get involved in that?
I don't remember reading about him in
the Bible stories.
And it's a big bunny delivering
multicolored eggs and candy to the kids.
Probably should be a big magic chicken.
I got in a big fight with one of my
friends about that. He said, "Brian, it
can't be the Easter chicken cuz chickens
have wings. They couldn't carry the
baskets."
That's your argument right there, you
idiot.
Carry the baskets?
I don't remember bunnies having hands
either, they're idiots.
>> But now my kids are older, so my kid my
son
just turned 23, just graduated from the
University of Delaware. So, yay!
I know, thank you. The blue hand. He's a
blue hand and now he's a waiter and he
lives at home. It's so great.
I'm so proud. It's so great. $200,000
and he's a waiter at home. How great is
that?
Yay, biology. Yay!
Yay!
Yay! Made $100 today. So happy. So
happy. So proud. So proud. It's a
challenge. It's a challenge, right? You
know? And I don't even know if like
colleges teach kids real life
experiences these days. I think they're
missing a gap a little bit. You know, so
here's his student loans are coming in,
right? And uh so we wanted to go to the
bank to uh well with his student loan
and they wanted to charge him $5 to pay
the bill online. I'm like, "That's
ridiculous. Let's go down to the bank
and open a checking account." What?
We'll go down to the bank and we'll open
a checking account.
How do you go in the bank? You go in the
bank.
Where are the doors? Behind the ATM. No,
there's not. Yes, there are.
There are doors and you go in the bank.
No, you don't. Yes, you do.
WHAT'S BACK THERE? PEOPLE.
WHAT DO THEY DO? THEY GIVE YOU A
CHECKING ACCOUNT.
WE WE WALKED THROUGH THE DOORS. IT WAS
LIKE DOROTHY.
YOU HAD NO IDEA. NO IDEA. CAME home he
had to write his first bill. Write his
first bill. $90. N I N D Y.
Oh, intelligent crowd. INTELLIGENT
CROWD. SOME SOME CROWDS DON'T GET THAT.
SOME CROWDS $200,000. THERE'S NO D IN
90. THERE'S NO D.
THERE'S NO SPELL CHECK FOR CHECKS.
THAT'S WHAT I'M DEALING WITH
MILLENNIALS.
But he figured it out and we talked
through it. We talked through it. We we
we did. And uh so he came back and he he
had the check all written out and he was
like, "I got it, Mom. I got it. Could I
get a stamp and an envelope?" And I was
like, "Yeah, I'll give you a stamp, but
you use the envelope it came with." He
goes, "No, I can't use that. It has a
HOLE IN IT."
$200,000.
SO PROUD.
We go out to dinner these nights, you
know, and he's like, "Oh, yeah, I'll
have the surf and turf." I'm like,
"Yeah, I'll have that steak medium
rare." And I'm like, "What happened to
chicken nuggets and a plastic cup of
milk?" Like, I just can't afford them
anymore. It just It just keeps Just
keeps happening. And I And I have a
daughter, she's 21.
Yeah, anyone else with that kind of joy,
pain, and agony in their life?
Oh my gosh.
It's just a weird time. Her hormones are
checking in, mine are completely
checking out. You know, just a weird
time in our lives. And uh she's up in
Canada for college, you know, cuz they
don't take SAT scores.
Oh, come on. You all have one. You all
have one that you know is just not quite
the brightest bulb in the box.
And if you're not laughing, you are that
bulb. Do you know what I'm saying?
You know.
Yes.
Canada. All right. That works. That
works. You know. You know right now. You
know right now.
Cuz she said stupid stuff all the time.
All the time. Here's an example. Here's
an example. We're going down to Maryland
for a little uh summer weekend, just the
two of us to meet friends that are all
down there. And she's sitting next to me
in the car, next to me. And she goes,
"Hey Mom, can you see me in your
rearview mirror?"
THANK YOU, SIR. YOU GOT THAT RIGHT AWAY.
YOU DID. I was like, "No, I cannot see
you or high school graduation."
What?
What are you talking about?
And there she is like a few years later.
She's in her teens, okay? We're walking
towards Target cuz I needed underwear.
They sell them in six-packs and
eight-packs at this point. That's how we
rock and roll at this age. That's how we
do it. That's how we do it. So, we're
walking towards Target. She finally
looks up from her phone and she goes,
"Hey Mom, what does the symbol FOR
TARGET MEAN?"
AGAIN, INTELLIGENT CROWD, intelligent
crowd.
What does the symbol for Target mean? I
just looked at her and go, "It means
COMMUNITY COLLEGE, HONEY."
SHE WENT, "DOES IT REALLY?" I was like,
"YES!
I'M SO SAVING ON THIS ONE. I AM."
SHE REALLY DOES. She hates that joke.
She does. She gets so annoyed. She's
like, "I mean, it's just a circle within
a circle." So makes IT A TARGET!
IT'S A LOT. IT'S A LOT TO KEEP UP WITH
MILLENNIALS. I'M trying really hard.
Oh, man. She gets me sometimes. She So
that she was up in Can- Canada. That's
where she is. And it was the first day
of spring. So I sent her a little text.
And I was like, "Yay, sweetie. First day
of spring. Hope things are warming up
for you up there in Canada. Love you,
Mom." And I put like a little Easter
bonnet, little Easter bonnet emoji, you
know, and sent it off.
Ding! And 2 seconds later I get back,
"Thanks, Mom. Why did you send me an
emoji of a taco?"
I didn't.
It's an Easter bonnet. And she was like,
"Put your glasses on. It's taco."
And she was right.
We were
so close.
So close. I love going home, too, cuz I
get to see my nieces.
So sweet. And they love my cell phone.
They love my cell phone cuz they use it
as a camera. They love to take pictures
of everything, themselves, everything.
They They just got a pet rabbit for
Easter. I don't know if y'all understand
how many pictures of this rabbit we
need, but it's a lot.
It's a lot of pictures of the rab- And
they figured out that the camera, you
know, you can flip it to take a picture
of the the rabbit. And then they flip it
back to take a picture of them. Picture
the rabbit. Picture them. Picture the
rabbit. And And they start that back and
forth with the camera going too fast, it
freezes up. And the little one got mad.
SHE WAS LIKE, "AUNT GIN, IT'S NOT
WORKING!"
I WAS LIKE, "Miss ma'am,
do you know what I had to go through at
your age to take a picture?"
It was a lot of click, CRANK, CRANK,
CRANK, CLICK, CRANK, CRANK, LIKE 30
SOMETHING TIMES. YOU DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
YOU HAD TO PICK. YOU DIDN'T GET TO SEE
IT RIGHT AWAY. YOU SENT THAT AWAY FOR A
WEEK.
A WEEK! YOU COULD HAVE 32 PICTURES OF
YOUR FINGER. YOU DIDN'T KNOW!
AND THEN FINALLY, AFTER YEARS OF THAT,
THEY CAME UP WITH ONE HOUR PROCESSING.
REMEMBER? OH, you're only going to have
to wait one hour for your pictures. Tell
me to wait an hour now for my pictures.
I will beat you like biscuit dough on
Sunday. Don't you even try that with me.
>> It was my daughter's kindergarten Easter
party, and I was instructed to bring
ambrosia on a stick.
Now, I didn't think giving swords to
five-year-olds was a good idea. Plus, I
didn't care.
So, I took what I had. I took
strawberries and marshmallow peeps and
shoved them on a toothpick and called it
a day.
Now, the problem was when I got up to
school and began handing out these
treats,
the juice from the strawberries
had fallen over the ears of the
marshmallow bunny,
and it looks like something out of Pet
Sematary
OR FATAL ATTRACTION.
HERE, CHILDREN, LET'S CELEBRATE our
risen Lord with this skewered BLEEDING
RABBIT.
PRINCESS PINTEREST WAS NOT happy with
me,
and I got on the PTA do not call list
for the bake sale.
But my husband had a completely
different approach to school.
Like when he drove carpool, he would
treat it like a military operation.
Like he'd have the kids standing in the
minivan with their backpacks on looking
like they're paratroopers.
He'd pull into the parking lot, SLOW
DOWN JUST ENOUGH FOR THE DOOR TO SLIDE
OPEN YELLING, "GO, GO, GO! PACK AND
ROLL! PACK AND ROLL!"
HE GOT BANNED FROM CARPOOL. SO, I THINK
that was his point all along.
>> I uh I took my family down to uh Myrtle
Beach, South Carolina last year for
Easter. My in-laws moved to Myrtle
Beach. And so for Easter, we just
decided we'd go down there and visit,
all right? They moved there a few years
ago and we're just going to go down and
have like nice weather, play a little
golf, maybe go to the beach, just have a
nice relaxing week, okay? But when we
decided that, it became a big thing. My
sister-in-law and her three girls, we're
going to come down, too. And aunts AND
UNCLES, WE'LL ALL COME DOWN. SO NOW
WE'RE GOING TO BE ONE family in one
house for A WEEK.
YEAH!
AND EVERYBODY'S HAD FAMILY VACATIONS,
OKAY? And they're brutal, okay? And we
had a day, there's really bad weather.
It just rained all day. When that
happens and you're at the beach, there's
nothing you can do. You can't spread out
from everybody. You know what I'm
saying? Family vacation for a week, you
need some spread out hours during a day.
When it rains, can't go to the beach,
can't play golf. Now we're all just
sitting around the house and everybody's
thinking, "Where are the knives?"
SO AT ONE POINT, SOMEBODY SAID, "HEY, WE
should all go shopping." And I WAS LIKE,
"OH, YEAH! YOU ALL SHOULD GO SHOPPING."
NO, WE'RE ALL going to go. OH, WELL.
SO, WE ALL go shopping. And what I do
when I get there is I take my niece, my
youngest niece, the one who's been
whining about everything. I'M BORED. I
DON'T LIKE IT. I I take her and put her
in a cart, so I can take her and just
whip her around aisles.
I love it. I do it hard and fast. SHE
THINKS IT'S A ride and I'm entertained.
I'm like, "YEAH, YEAH, YEAH." I GOT TO
whip her. Like, SHE'LL SHE'LL CRACK A
HEAD.
NOT HARD, JUST ENOUGH TO sleep for A
LITTLE WHILE.
SO, THERE'S ONE POINT WE CAME AROUND
this corner WE HAD TO STOP CUZ THERE
WERE PEOPLE COMING TOWARD US AND they
hate it when you hit them. So, I
stopped.
And it happened to be a black couple.
And we had that pause where we just
didn't know which side we're going to go
to.
So, during that pause, my niece stands
up in the CART AND SAYS, "HELLO, BLACK
PEOPLE!"
THEY WERE AS STUNNED AS I WAS.
I WAS LIKE, "WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,
HEY!" "YOU CAN'T SAY THAT." "WHY?"
"I DON'T KNOW."
SHE DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG. LIKE,
"YOU'RE GOING TO GET US KILLED." "WHY?"
"I DON'T KNOW."
THAT ONE CAN GET AWKWARD. HE SAID,
"BLACK PEOPLE." I KNOW, I DO. And I have
to cuz I don't know what kind of black
they were. I know there's different
kind. There's coffee, latte, mocha. I
don't know what they were. I know with
white people, we're all white, okay?
Nobody's ever said, "You're white, but
you
you're more eggshell."
I don't know.
But I'm done with the family holidays.
Done. All right, not just that week was
so bad, the lead-up to it from Christmas
till Easter, same conversation with my
in-laws any time they called. Any in-law
every time, same conversation. This
Easter, we are going to get you an
Easter Bunny costume.
No, you can dress up like an Easter
Bunny. You're funny, you're a comedian.
We'll all chip in and get you an Easter
Bunny costume.
No, it'll be funny. You're funny, you're
a comedian, the children love you. We'll
all chip in, get you an Easter Bunny
costume. YOU GOT YOU CAN BE A FUNNY
BUNNY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT ABOUT THIS? What about instead,
what if I go out, I get a Jesus costume
and I come back in 3 days?
So anyway, growing up in Bellevue,
fantastic.
Uh one time I remember me and my brother
were at this church activity where we
were painting Easter eggs for homeless
people.
Think about that for a minute, you guys.
It's like borderline disrespectful.
It's very condescending.
Here, homeless dude, a decorative Easter
egg.
I hope it keeps you warm and solves your
financial problems.
What?
Oh, yeah, see, we're rich, so we paint
our food.
Try to stay dry.
Happy Easter.
It's disrespectful.
So, I wasn't taking it seriously. I was
just writing the names of my favorite
rap groups on the eggs.
Like the Wu-Tang Clan.
Loved listening to them growing up.
And this lady sees what I'm doing. She
gets one of my eggs. She brings it over
to me. She's like, "Lam, I don't know
what Wu-Tang means,
but I'm pretty sure it's not
appropriate."
This is where I could lie and use my
minority status to my advantage. I was
like, "Actually, Wu-Tang is an African
tribe.
It's part of my culture.
Please respect that."
She was very apologetic. She's like,
"Lamo, I'm so sorry. I didn't know." I
took the lie a step further, you guys. I
told her that in Africa, we throw up a W
sign to say Wu-Tang. It means hello.
She believed me.
The next week in church, this lady gets
up to give a talk.
She's like, "Good morning, brothers and
sisters. WU-TANG!"
"WU-TANG IS AN AFRICAN GREETING that I
learned from Lamo over there.
I'm very cultured."
I shot her in the head with a dart, you
guys. I had to.
I was like, "How's that for an African
greeting?"
She left me no choice.
>> You know what holidays really changed in
my in my lifetime culturally? Easter.
Cuz my nieces and nephews, they they
open pre- These kids expect presents for
Easter. I go, "Whoa, times have changed,
man. When I was a kid, my father didn't
even color the Easter eggs. He just
bought brown eggs.
And he hid them in the same spot every
year, behind the mayonnaise in the
fridge. That was it.
If you found them, good. Make me an
omelet. Okay, I got you.
Now I got you, punch.
>> I've been married I've been robbed 31
times. Yep, 31 bank robberies, right?
The first bank robbery, I was young,
right? I was 18. It was actually Good
Friday, and all the bank tellers were
dressed up in their Easter outfits. It
was really cute. I was dressed as a
rabbit.
A 6-ft tall rabbit with ears that went
up about 10 ft, right?
That was, you know, something you did
back then, right?
And a guy comes up to the teller next to
me and all I hear is, "Put the money in
the bag." And I'm like,
"That sounds like my wife."
But he had a mustache. So, I'm still,
you know, what are you going to do? He
could still be my wife.
It's okay. We love each other, you
Well, one thing they do, if you've ever
worked in a bank, they tell you don't
run after a bank robber. Just give them
the money and let them go. Not me. I'm
going to be a hero. I ran after him.
Dressed as a rabbit.
I had the floppy feet coming out to
here. I'm running down the street like
this. One of my feet fell off, right? A
homeless guy picked it up. He's rubbing
it going, "Here comes Peter Cottontail."
You know, it was a weird experience.
The guy pointed the gun at me, but he
didn't shoot cuz you wouldn't shoot the
Easter Bunny, right?
And he got away. He got away. What's
really weird is 30 years later, right?
I'm working in another office. I'm the
manager there.
And I had one of these tellers, her name
was Margo. She was 65 years old. She was
a veteran, right?
Guy comes up,
robs her, and she he's got a gun. She
reaches out and grabs the gun out of his
hand.
She says, "You need to go back to
school. WHAT WOULD YOUR PARENTS THINK
ABOUT THIS?"
AND SHE'S WAVING the gun around.
He walks outside, sits down on the
curb, and starts weeping.
Yeah. The police showed up. We found out
that as a child, he'd been traumatized.
He had seen a rabbit chasing a bank
robber.
>> Good night, everybody. There any church
folks here? We got church people here in
the crowd a little bit, okay? Thank you,
church faithful.
I don't know. I mean, church is weird,
though. I love church, but it was a
little strange, man. You know, did y'all
have the first 5 months of the pandemic
2020 where your pastor's just preaching
to an empty room and a camera like a
hostage video. Did y'all go through that
phase?
He's just reading a list of demands.
They're treating us well.
It's weird.
No, church is weird though, man. But
then we started getting back together.
It was pretty cool June or so of 2020.
Started to be kind of people kind of
scared, but we started getting And then
Cracker Barrel opened the same week. I
was like, "The earth is healing itself."
I was so excited. I knew we'd turned the
corner.
But then my wife's friend wants to come
out with us, you know, to lunch. Her Her
name is Stacy and my wife's friend is a
vegetarian. Now, Stacy's fine. She's a
sweet lady, but she's a little pushy.
She's a little judgmental, okay? And if
you're vegetarian here today, hey, fine.
Eat whatever you want to eat. But I was
like, "I want to invite her to Cracker
Barrel, but what's she going to eat at
Cracker Barrel, okay?"
They cook their green beans in hog lard.
What can she have? The box? What's left?
My wife was like, "It'll be okay."
Y'all, it wasn't okay. I'm having my
old-timer's breakfast, holding my piece
of bacon like an American.
And I can feel Stacy's eyes on me the
whole meal. Finally, I was like, "What?"
She said, "DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW THEY MAKE THAT?"
I SAID, "I DON'T, BUT YOU TELL THEM
THEY'RE nailing it because
this is like a hug from Jesus.
He's real, y'all. He's real.
And if you're a vegetarian here tonight,
please don't be offended. I want you to
feel welcome. Don't be offended. I mean,
I'm not afraid of you charging the stage
and attacking me. You're far too weak.
What I'm saying is like, don't try.
It's a lot of steps. You could get
woozy, couldn't you?
Church is a little weird though. Some
churches put stencils on the walls. I've
noticed since you go to churches though,
like put stuff on the walls. White
people do this a lot. This I I blame
Chip and Joanna Gaines for this culture.
You ever walk in somebody's house live,
laugh, love on the wall? What is that?
What are you doing?
On my wall I want live, laugh, leave.
That's what I want. Get out.
But my church I've been to a church
before my church puts like our core
values and some scriptures on the walls.
I went to a church a few months ago and
they had the 10 Commandments on the
wall. And it wasn't just like all
together it was like scattered
throughout the church just randomly. So
weird the placement of some of these
Commandments. Like over the pastor's
office I swear to you it said, "Thou
shalt not kill."
I WAS LIKE, "WHAT HAPPENED IN PASTOR'S
OFFICE? What do I need to know?"
Good grief.
But one thing I really did enjoy I got
to plug in at my church you know more
that was kind of cool. We started
working in the nursery y'all anybody
work in the nursery at your church? You
got to do it it's the best cuz these
babies cannot rat you out if it all goes
wrong.
You come back after church I hand you a
crying baby it's like look maybe I
dropped him maybe he's a brat. Like you
know.
YOU DON'T GET TO JUDGE ME THIS is the
Lord's house okay?
And we're a sticker church I'll put in
stickers on the kids when you check them
in at your church. These big churches do
it we're tagging these kids like they're
in the wild it's weird.
Like it's a nature study. Sprinkle out
some goldfish crackers and track their
movements.
My pastor had to explain it to me Johnny
it's a security thing it's got the kids
name on the sticker code at the bottom.
Parent gets piece of paper with that
same code they come back after church
you know to claim their child like it's
a coat check or a raffle. Wonderful.
And parents lose that piece of paper at
my church I don't know what your policy
is at your church but I don't put up
with that mess in my nursery.
You come back without that paper I'm
like I'm sorry we're keeping him okay?
He works for Jesus all right? YOU KNEW
THE RISKS.
BUT LIKE, YOU KNOW ME, THAT'S MY SON. I
JUST DROPPED HIM OFF. I'm like, "Sir,
look, okay?
Without the receipt,
the best I CAN DO IS STORE CREDIT."
AND THEN I LET HIM PICK OUT A CHILD OF
EQUAL OR lesser value.
We give out so many redheads, y'all.
It's unbelievable.
I used to drink. I don't drink. I hadn't
drank in coming 4 years in June that I
have not drank. I feel GOOD ABOUT THAT.
A LOT OF STORIES. Not going to bore you
with them.
Uh
I used to like to go to breakfast drunk.
3:00 in the morning. You ever do that?
3:00 a.m. Denny's, IHOP.
Ugh. Here's what you do. Next time
you're like with your friends 3:00 in
the morning, do this. Order the biggest
breakfast on the menu. When they get to
the part where they ask you what kind of
eggs you want, just be like,
"Uh Easter, and could you hide them from
me?"
And stare at them till it's awkward.
Uh the menu says two eggs any style, and
the style I have chosen is Easter, so.
Oh, no. If you want to get a manager, do
what you got to do. Look, I
I was not prepared.
I don't want to tell you how to do your
job.
When I was a kid, I collected comic
books.
Now, people refer to me as a hoarder.
I don't like how that has changed.
Uh and I really loved holidays as a kid,
you know, Halloween, especially
Halloween and Easter, two of my favorite
holidays. Obviously, because candy's
involved in both of them.
And I definitely look like I like candy.
Uh
Yeah, and as a kid, you would wait for
the I would wait for the Easter Bunny to
come bring me a basket full of candy.
Now, I play the Easter Bunny at a mall.
That was a big change.
That was a big change. But, let me tell
you,
uh, playing the Easter Bunny was a great
job. It really was. Because kids TREAT
THE EASTER BUNNY LIKE A CELEBRITY. CUZ
WHEN HE COMES ROLLING INTO THE MALL,
THEY KNOW THEY SEE THIS magical creature
that's going to hide Easter eggs and
candy. They don't see what he really is.
Just an overweight out of work stand up
comic trying to raise money for booze to
drink to forget how he ended up in the
MALL IN A BUNNY SUIT.
YEAH, THAT'S MAGICAL.
I'm not good at keeping jobs.
Even my Even my job when I graduated
college, um, so I graduated and, uh,
but I thought with the college degree I
would get some sort of grown-up job.
Something boring, 9-5, I don't know.
Best job I could land when I graduated
college
was an Easter Bunny at the mall.
And I'll be honest, this backdrop is
giving me some severe flashbacks to that
job.
They They hired me.
In the interview they even said like,
"Well, Mr. Harden, we'll we'll take you,
but to be honest, you're you're over
qual- over qualified."
I was like, "All right, is that cuz I
went to college?" They're like, "No, you
passed THE DRUG TEST."
NO ONE'S DONE THAT YET. YOU GOT my job
at the end of this.
They were asking me serious job
interview questions.
They had their paper out like, "So, Mr.
um,
where do you see yourself in 5 years?"
I don't know, Santa.
I thought this job would end at Easter.
I didn't know there was a 5-year plan,
so.
My boss was 15 years old.
That got messy.
Getting yelled at, like, "You need to
get to work on time."
Like, "Well, then stop asking me to pick
you up from school."
The biggest worry about being an Easter
bunny,
kids do not like the bunny.
Moms, you want the picture with your kid
and the bunny. That kid is used to
seeing a fluffy little cute bunny,
goes to the mall, now it's 6-ft tall,
doesn't blink, that's demonic.
I had a toddler not wanting the picture
with me. The mom is forcing him on my
lap. The kid's already crying.
Runs away, she pulls him back up by his
shirt collar, throws him back on my lap.
He's kicking, screaming, crying, trying
to get away. She's strong-holding him on
my lap.
This is going on for 10 minutes.
I feel so bad for this kid, I finally
yell, I'm like, "Hey, stop it. Leave him
alone. He doesn't want it."
BUT I'M IN THIS GIANT BUNNY HEAD, so all
they heard was
And they still couldn't hear me, so I
finally just rip off the bunny head.
>> They both look at me traumatized,
scared to death.
And that's the picture the photographer
took.
I was always messing with my my Sunday
school teachers, too. Like I would
hear the stories and I'd be like, "Hey,
well, I have some follow-up questions
and thoughts." And that's really how I
started as a comedian, just dealing with
Sunday school teachers. Like, you know?
There's one where we were talking about
Jesus and how he didn't get married and
I go, "I think I know why Jesus wasn't
married." And the teacher goes, "What?
Oh, okay, why?" And I go, "Well, cuz um
you can't stay sinless with a
mother-in-law, right? It doesn't work,
right? No,
right?
EVEN THE SON OF GOD would start to lose
his temper
with that.
Even during his miracles, she'd be
nagging him about stuff. Like, she'd go,
"Oh,
oh, what's that?
Oh, Jesus turned all of the water into
wine, did he? Well, unfortunately, some
of us wanted water. I'm a little
parched.
Oh, we got some wine now, great. Great.
How about this? Won't you get one of
those 12 idiots to scrounge me up an
Aquafina? That would be a miracle."
Told her to marry the dentist.
"Dr. Herskovitz, he'll take care of you,
you know?" "Oh, I have to marry the
broke Messiah.
Okay.
Get a job, Jesus. That'll be a miracle,
right?"
Couldn't do it.
Then you know, around Easter time, we
start talking about the Last Supper and
I was like, "Ooh, I got one." She's
like, "Please don't. Please don't." I'm
like, "No, I just think that the Last
Supper is like the most uncomfortable
awkward meal in history, All Cuz Jesus
is wanting to make this a very special
moment for his 12 closest friends, and
he's using some metaphors, and he says,
"Look, this is my body, and this is my
blood. It's It's for you. Take and
remember me. Eat it and drink it."
Problem is,
these are 12 idiots that have not
understood a word he has said for the
past 3 years. They have no idea what
he's talking about. You could see it
right there in the text. It is It's
almost subtext. They're just kind of
like, "Wait a second. Does Jesus want us
to eat him? Like,
I'm not sure if I I was cool leaving my
job, but I don't know about this part
here."
No, no. I'll I'll get some later.
Thanks. Yes.
I'm going to I'm no carbs right now.
Yes, please.
Something else about that meal that is a
little uncomfortable and awkward is
Judas showed up
after he betrayed Jesus. There's only
one word for that. Tacky. Come on now.
You can't show up to that meal
afterwards. But, I love the way that
Jesus treats it. Because Jesus treats it
like any parent here would when you go
home and there's a broken vase, and you
know what kid broke the vase, but you
want them to confess to it. All right?
And so, Jesus goes,
"One of you has betrayed me."
Problem is, Judas does not confess.
Peter's so dumb, he tries to do it. He's
like, "Was it me, Lord?" And she's like,
"No, dude. It's not you."
You would know if it was you.
I got to get some new friends.
So, that was part of, you know, that's
just how I grew up. And so, uh now being
in New York City, like I said, they
they've got Catholics, and I'm trying to
get adjusted to that. Uh one of my good
friends there in New York is Catholic.
He's like, "Dude, we got to take you to
an old school Roman Catholic mass,
right? You see how they used to do it,
man. They you're going to love this.
It's just like your church service back
home. You're going to love this." And
so, I went. And the thing is, I'd never
been to a Roman Catholic mass before.
So, I didn't know this guy that was up
in front of everybody. I don't know if
you guys know this guy, but he's like,
I'm like, "I think there's something
wrong with your preacher, right? I think
he had a stroke or something cuz he's
like moaning at people right now." My
friend's like, "No, man, this is part of
the It's like your sermon back home."
I'm like, "This is not like my sermon
back home. Like, we have preachers. We
don't have this guy right here. This guy
sounds like he's apologizing for how
boring it is.
I'm sorry this is boring."
A preacher's going to put the Holy
Spirit in you whether you want him there
or not, right? Like, "Welcome to the
holy tabernacle of the Lord Jesus
Christ, right?"
Think I can't compete?
He had one title to his name, Father.
Father McNeil. I'm like, "Oh, you must
be new cuz a preacher's got all the
titles, right? Like, I'm the Dr.
Reverend here. I'm the Dr. Reverend
Preacher Pastor. I'm the Dr. Reverend
Preacher Pastor Bishop Deacon Johnson
Jr. the third."
Then afterwards, he's like, "Would you
like to go in this little box and tell
me your secrets?" No, I would not.
YEAH, MID- MIDWESTERN CHRISTIANS, WE
don't tell people our sins. We stuff
them down inside and never tell anyone
ever.
>> I tend to get like really attached
really quickly when I date someone.
That's kind of like my go-to move.
That's my thing.
And people will always say it's a bad
idea. You know, they're like, you know,
only fools rush in. Don't put all your
eggs in one basket. Which is fine, but
like, where else do you want me to put
my eggs, man?
Right? Where else if not this basket?
And do I look like the guy who has like
an abundance of other baskets available
to him?
Right.
Got to put them somewhere. Have you
tried carrying around a bunch of eggs?
They just fall everywhere. You have to
put them in a basket.
Just looking for somewhere to put my
eggs.
It's actually what my Tinder bio says.
Just
Got to put those eggs somewhere.
Got to cherish, especially when you got
kids going to church. That's the worst.
You got the kids loading them up. They
don't want to go when they're that
young. They They want to go for the
social aspect, but they don't want to
get up and go. You got to get them
dressed. You got to fight them to get
dressed. And hey, let's get a hurry up.
And you start losing it. You start
getting that
vein in the forehead. LIKE, HURRY UP!
YOU GOT TO GET them all in. That's why I
show up late, man. I'm late, dude. I am
late late arriving to any church
anything just late. That's my strategy.
Late. You show UP TOO EARLY, OH, OH, HE
MUST KNOW. NO, NO, NO, NO. I'm here to
blend in. I'm in the back. I am back row
Joe is what I am. I
If they won't If they move the wall
farther back, that's where I would be.
I'm not kidding you. Just keep scooting
it back. I am back there rolling in with
my kids and my wife. And you got to get
packed. You got to bring supplies. You
have to get everything. You You to get
beef jerky, flaming hot Cheetos.
You got to get the iPad charged up. And
by the way, can you get some signal in
there, for crying out loud? What is
going on?
How am I going to find the score if I
don't
This tough.
THIS TOUGH. I AM back row Joe, all the
way in the back, and you got your kids,
and you're just trying to keep them
behaved. You want to keep every You just
want to blend in and you're like, "Okay,
shh, just okay." And you have to
separate them. You have to be in the
middle, cuz if you let them all sit in
one clump, you know that it's trouble.
So, you have to kind of break it up and
like, "Okay, here's some Cheerios. Shut
up. Just be
quiet." About four rows up, you get,
"What's wrong with him? What's his
problem? Can't he You can't control your
children." Like, "Shut up, or I'll snap
your neck. Do you understand?"
Seriously.
And don't you know how to raise your
kids? No, I have no idea what I'm doing.
I'm winging it, believe me, man.
And I know my parents are winging it,
cuz if they weren't, I wouldn't be doing
this for a living. I could tell you
that.
I'd have a respectable job. I wouldn't
be selling
people dog food.
Sure.
Man.
You go to these things and someone's got
to say the prayer. It's like, "Oh man,
keep it tight. Let's go. Let's go."
You know, when someone They Sometimes
they need to ask someone right on the It
needs to be extemporaneous. "You say the
prayer." OKAY, ALL RIGHT, THEN IT'LL BE
QUICK. You tell someone a week in
advance, oh no. They're going to go
through it all. They're going to cover
every possible subject in the world,
wars and rumors of wars and moisture and
moisture moisture. Thank you, moisture.
Need moisture. We got moisture. I get
it. I get
But we CAN DO THAT.
UH THESE ARE THE REASONS THEY DON'T ASK
ME TO TALK AT CHURCH, BY the way. This
is exactly why.
I think men and women in general, we
just have different tempers. The way we
process anger is just different. Me
personally, I have an amnesia temper.
I'll get upset and forget why I'm mad in
the same sentence.
I'll be like, "YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M HUNGRY."
WE GO TO CHURCH TOGETHER. We go to a
non-denominational church, you know. We
grew up in different cultures, but we
also grew up in different church
cultures. Like she grew up in the
Catholic church and I grew up in the
Pentecostal.
That's where I get my moves from.
WITH THE CHOIR, YEAH.
I I CHICAGO.
I love this guy. What is happening right
now?
We made a commitment we would visit each
other's churches
um when we got married
and I wasn't prepared for the workout
that I was about to have.
Catholic church, they they got pews and
there's a pew behind you and one in
front of you. They're really hard wood
and I didn't know there's equipment
built in and that's for praying.
And there's not a lot of room in my
wife's side. We've got to put the
equipment down.
Like, what is this an Airbnb? Are we
staying the night?
There's no room to put it down.
YOU NEED SPACE FOR THAT. And we fold it
down and you have to get this knee and
you got to put the knee
I'm the kneeler.
Thank you.
I started looking like the Tin Man. I'M
LIKE, "I NEED OIL."
COME ON, PRIEST. BRING IT OVER.
NEED THE OIL. I'm cramping up.
And then you got to get this knee.
And you put your elbow here and you put
your elbow here and you put it together.
And as soon as you do that, the priest
goes, "Please stand."
"Please kneel." Oh, we're going down?
That was a short prayer.
Wasn't prepared. I got bad knees. Hold
on. "Please stand." Okay.
"Please kneel." Oh, we're going down
again. "Please stand." My wife's like,
"We got TO KNEEL." I'M WORKING ON IT.
"PLEASE STAND."
"PLEASE KNEEL."
PRIEST GOES, "Please sit." My wife's
like, "WHY AREN'T YOU STANDING?" HE SAID
I COULD TAKE A BREAK.
"PLEASE STAND." "PLEASE SIT." OH, we're
doing crunches?
It's like a Zumba class I didn't sign up
for.
And then we went to my church that
night, the Pentecostal.
We don't even have a band.
IT'S LIKE AN AEROBIC CHURCH.
As you can see, I haven't been to that
church for a while.
I'm a churchy GUY. CHURCHY PEOPLE?
ALL RIGHT, NOBODY? OKAY. UH
>> HALLELUJAH.
>> FOUND THE BAPTIST?
NO, MAN. I'M I'M A SINGLE GUY. I'M
SINGLE IN CHURCH. IT'S TOUGH BEING
SINGLE in church cuz they expect me to
do everything. Every Every Sunday my
pastor's like, "Hey, uh we're re-tarring
the roof at 4:00 a.m. See you there."
No, you won't.
My phone's going to be off.
Damn, man. I I like going to church. I
got baptized in the church. Pentecostal.
Hallelujah.
I did it. It's in Florida. I'm pretty
sure they put ice in the bucket when
they did it cuz I went in there, I came
up with hypothermia. I came out and I
was like, "Ah sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh
sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh sh."
AND THEN HE'S GOT THE HOLY SPIRIT.
JESUS.
OH.
IT'S TOUGH DATING IN THE CHURCH, isn't
it? Oh my Here's the problem. Like when
you cuz when you have a good
conversation with somebody, it's always
awkward. I'm an awkward guy. No, like
just normal people conversations, group
conversations, awkward. Like I was doing
a church show in Tulsa, Oklahoma, right?
And as I was leaving the stage, I said
this. Said, "All right, y'all. See you
in heaven."
Doesn't that sound like the nicest way
OF MURDERING EVERYONE?
RIGHT?
JUST PASSING OUT. ALL RIGHT, here's your
cool date. you there. You know, like
that's not
So, I'm at church. I'm having a great
conversation with this lady, right? We
we we connected. We were talking about
stuff. We had a lot of stuff in common.
She starts talking about hobbies. She
goes, "What do you do?" I said, "Well,
I'm a stand-up comic. Sometimes people
laugh."
I said, "Well, what do you do in your
spare time?" And she said she likes to
square dance.
And I was like, "Well, we both make bad
decisions. Okay.
All right.
Let's do this."
SO, WE'RE SITTING THERE TALKING and this
old lady at my church, she comes she
comes right in butts right in the
conversation. Goes, "What's your
favorite Bible verse?"
And I had to tell her, right? Because he
has no time left. And
Told her mine is Psalm 82:3-4,
right? Which is defend the weak and the
fatherless, uphold the rights of the
poor and destitute, rescue the weak and
the needy, deliver them from the hands
of the wicked. Which, right? Even if
you're not Christian, you can be against
slavery, stand up for the oppressed. We
can all get behind that, right?
Right?
She's walking away and I was like,
"Ma'am, what's your
favorite Bible verse?" She looks back
and she goes, "Psalm 137:9."
If you're not familiar, I wasn't
I looked it up. Psalm 137:9 says,
"Blessed is he
who takes your children
and bashes them against the rock."
I looked at this lady and I was like,
"Oh, no.
We got to get her out of that nursery.
Uh
Some of you guys don't like that. That's
fine. That's all right.
THAT'S HOW I FELT. CUZ YOU KNOW HOW YOU
CUZ YOU'RE LIKE, you know, "Fool me
once, shame on you. Fool me twice, shame
on the ring. You know, fool me three
times, we're running out of children."
So, you know, it's just
>> I own two children. I own uh
I own two American kids, little ones.
Round of applause if you're a parent,
any young parent. You're nice.
Nice. How many kids do you have?
>> Three.
>> Three kids. One of each?
>> Uh
Yes.
>> Okay.
A boy, girl, boy, what do you what do
you have?
>> Two girls, a boy.
>> Okay, two girls and a boy. That's
lovely. That's Did you have a dance
recital yet for the girl? And she's into
dance, she does that? No?
>> No.
>> Any kids into dance?
No? Are you have a kid into dance?
Oh, sorry. I thought you put your hand
up. My daughter had her very first dance
recital, little girl. And she had her
very first dance recital the other day.
And it was in front of a thousand people
in this auditorium. She looked about
this big on the stage. Monstrous. She
looked about a 4-minute solo all by
herself. And
and halfway through her routine, I got
choked up.
I got very teary-eyed because seeing my
little girl alone on that stage, I
realized as a father, I have been
wasting so much money on dance lessons.
She's absolutely terrible. I was like,
"What is this? This is No. No, her dress
cost more than my car. That's
ridiculous."
It's tough having kids, not easy, right?
It's not easy. I
I grew up in Ireland, obviously, right?
I grew up in Ireland. Very religious
country. I like that. I believe in God.
And so, so to teach my kids. I had to
teach my kids about religion. I had to
teach my kids about God. So I said to my
daughter, "All right, I'm going to teach
you how to pray." That's God 101. You
can't mess that up. It's a prayer. It's
something simple. You ready, honey?
Follow me. Do this. You ready? In the
name of the Father, the Son, and the
Holy Spirit. Immediately she stopped me.
Right out the gate she had a question.
"Daddy, why do you bless yourself before
a prayer?"
Now instead of me having the
intelligence or the patience to explain
in the name of the Father, Son, and the
Holy Spirit, I said,
"Did you ever send an email?"
"Well, a prayer, it's kind of like an
email to God.
But before you send an email,
you have to log in."
And then after you send an email, then
you have to log out.
She says, "What happens if I forget to
log out?" Well, that's fine. Everything
you say keeps going to God, but it goes
into a spam folder.
Um
"What happens if God's Wi-Fi is not
working?" Oh, I don't know, honey. I'm
pretty sure God has 5G. Uh
"Who's going to fix God's Wi-Fi?" Oh, I
don't know. I'm I'm sure like now this
kid is so confused that she thinks God
is some guy up in heaven on a floating
cloud who's on the phone to India, uh
some guy in tech support wondering why
he can't get someone to come out to fix
his Wi-Fi till the 28th of the month
when he built the whole universe in 6
days. That's exhausting.
It's exhausting explaining religion to
my children. Religious holidays, that's
one of the hardest ones to ever explain
to my kids, religious holidays. Like
Easter. Easter, listen, we celebrate it
a little bit different in Ireland. In
Ireland we celebrate Easter slightly
differently you do in America because in
America,
you hide eggs.
You celebrate one of the holiest days of
the year BY HIDING POULTRY.
BUT THEN I WENT BACK, I READ THE BOOK,
OKAY, that on Good Friday Jesus died for
our sins. While he was gone, all his
friends hid the eggs.
Um
Easter Sunday, he rose again. He said,
"Where did you put the eggs, lads? Where
did you
Where are the eggs? Where are the Peter,
where did you Come on, where are the
eggs?
Peter, where are the eggs? Yeah, Judas
said, "No, you know where they are."
Peter, where
So, MY KIDS ARE SPOILED. SO, I
SPENT I'VE GOT THIS BIG BAG OF EGGS THAT
I WAS up till like 4:00 in the morning
hand painting them the night before. And
you can't just throw your eggs about
your yard willy-nilly, cuz kids are
spoiled. We want to give them a good
experience. We have to have a strategy
with every location. Like, let me take
this one egg and I'll I'll put it here
behind the flower pot, cuz when the sun
drifts by at approximately 11:14, it'll
shine on that egg, create a glow in my
son's heart that can only be matched if
Santa Claus and Elmo got and threw him
his own party to chop the puppy firework
factory, right?
Let me take the blue egg and move it far
away from the red egg, cuz they're gang
colors, apparently, right? And we can't
have those mixing.
But about 10 eggs in, you don't care
anymore. You're like, "Ah, you know
what? I'll be here all day. That's
ridiculous. What's that? Poison ivy? Who
doesn't LOVE TO SCRATCH?
WHO DOESN'T LOVE TO SCRATCH?
NOW, MY son is a bit slow, so he's got
nothing in his basket. It's getting
dark. You feel bad for him, so you kind
of have to help him out a wee bit,
right? You're like, "Oh, look, come
here. If If you look hard enough, maybe
you'll find that the Easter Bunny left
one right behind the flower If YOU LOOK
HARD ENOUGH,
MAYBE YOU'LL MAYBE Maybe You know
what? It's right there. Look, it's right
there. There it is. THAT'S A PINK EGG ON
GREEN GRASS. CAN YOU NOT SEE THAT?
STOP PICKING YOUR NOSE.
A LOT OF OLD GAMES AT THE GOODWILL. I
got this. This is Probe.
Yeah, uh
Parker Brothers put this out in 1965.
And I did my due diligence and uh
that's all that's in there.
In the game of Probe.
Well, games were simpler back then.
I I love America. I'm a I'm a true
American. In fact, I had to buy this.
It's a boxing glove. Isn't that cool?
And it says right there, "Made in
Pakistan."
Uh a lot of great Oh, you know what they
have there that I really love? A lot of
arts and crafts. People make these arts
and crafts. You look like an arts and
crafter, are you, Jason?
You have a little shop?
This is really cool. Someone made this.
An aunt is like a mom, but cooler.
Isn't that neat? And on the back it
says, "An uncle is like a dad, but
creepier."
Look what I got for you, Jason. It's a
participation trophy.
Thanks for just showing up.
What's your What was that? I'm sorry.
>> Well, I don't I have one. Everyone
should have one if you
>> What What is your name, young man?
>> Will.
>> Will, how old are you?
>> 13.
>> 13. Let me teach you something real
quick.
Life isn't fair, Will.
One day you're going to have to LEAVE
PROVO.
I THINK I HANDLED THAT WELL.
THIS IS MY ADVICE TO ALL OF YOU,
ESPECIALLY YOU, MY FRIEND. Look at that.
What is your name?
Blue? I don't even want to know.
It's really none of my business, isn't
it?
Blue, you look great. You got some great
tats you got there. Some tats I don't
have any tats. I have some moles I
should have checked.
But my advice from you, Lou Blue, don't
ever buy marijuana from the Easter
Bunny.
Hang on. I want to keep THAT JOKE FRESH.
CAN'T GET ANY MORE OF THIS TILL MARCH.
>> When you go to church, I've learned
there's a different language in church.
Words mean different thing.
Like you can hear somebody say, "Good to
see you, brother."
Translation, I forgot your name.
Or you could hear someone say, "The Lord
has put something on my heart today."
Translation, "Hey, you got a truck? You
can help me move."
Or you could hear your pastor say
something like uh "Hey, brother, are you
coming to Bible study after service?"
And you can say, "I'll pray about it."
Translation, "No."
Game starts in an hour. I got pulled
pork in the crock pot. Not today, Satan.
Not today.
My parents have a strong faith. That's
why I was always in a church. Uh they're
really wonderful, generous people. My
mom is probably one of the nicest ladies
in the entire world. She's just a saint.
She remembers everyone's birthday,
anniversary, special event. She's always
got a card and a gift for them. She's so
nice. She has a room in her house full
of random gifts in case someone shows up
unexpectedly.
The other day there's a knock on the
door and she answers it and she goes,
"No, I don't want to join the Jehovah's
Witness, but here's a bread maker. God
bless you."
There's your loaves. Now just find some
fishes. You're halfway there.
Kids, man, I love my kids.
Uh 10-year-old boy, 8-year-old daughter.
Um my daughter, she's gorgeous, man.
Blonde hair, blue eyes, gorgeous little
girl. I remember when she was four.
Oh, she was so cute, right? She loved
me. Right? She had the little chubby
cheeks, right?
And she was so sweet until she didn't
get what she wanted.
Right?
Never failed. Right before bedtime, she
looked at me because she knows I'm weak,
right?
She'd put on the face and the voice.
Right? She'd look at me, she'd be like,
"Daddy?"
"DADDY?"
"CAN I HAVE SOME CANDY?"
"CAN I HAVE SOME CANDY, DADDY?
PLEASE?"
BUT NO, SWEETIE, YOU CAN'T HAVE CANDY
RIGHT before bedtime. You'll be up all
night. No, you can't have any candy.
Then she turned into Gollum from Lord of
the Rings, that little evil creature in
the mountain, right?
She's like, "BUT I WANT IT SWEET,
DADDY."
"I WANT IT SWEET."
"OH, HE HITS DADDY. HE HITS HIM." "I
DON'T
LOVE DADDY. HE GIVES US CANDY
SOMETIMES." "NO, HE HITS HIM."
YEAH.
YES.
SCARED THE CRAP OUT OF ME.
THEN HER HEAD WOULD SPIN around and puke
juice all over me.
That's what happened.
But now she's eight. She's evolved.
She's gotten smarter, right? She's
gotten smarter, so now she still asks,
right before bedtime, she get up candy.
She's like,
"Daddy?"
"Can I have some candy?" Like, "No,
sweetie, you can't have candy right
before bedtime. We've been through this.
No, you can't have any candy. No. Go to
bed.
Okay, Daddy.
I'm like, WHAT WAS THAT?
SHE'S GOING TO KILL ME IN MY SLEEP.
WHAT IS GOING ON, MAN?
SO, HERE'S THE THING. I'M DOING LAUNDRY
the next day, right? Cuz I I'm like Mr.
Mom when I'm home. I do the laundry,
right? And I get there and I'm doing the
laundry. My wife's been teaching my
daughter how to journal or write her
feelings down and stuff, right?
So, I go by the room to drop off some
laundry.
I see the journal
on the bed.
Right? I know the moms in here are like,
no, you didn't. Yes, I did.
Yes, I did. Any father in here would,
right, sir? You you know.
If there's a lock on THAT THING, YOU'RE
BLOWING THAT BABY OPEN AND YOU'RE
LOOKING INSIDE.
RIGHT?
SO, I'm flipping through the journal.
What She's eight. YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WHAT SHE
FLIPPING THROUGH.
LOOKING.
There's all these accounts of Daddy
saying no. It's like, no, no. Daddy said
no. No candy. No candy. No No. No. I'm
like, oh my gosh, she hates me.
Right? And then I get to the last page
and apparently, she's got a crush on
some boy named Robbie WHO GIVES HER
CANDY AT SCHOOL.
I SAID, NOW, I'M SAYING NO AT HOME AND
SHE'S GETTING IT ON THE SIDE AT SCHOOL
FROM A LITTLE JERK NAMED ROBBIE.
NOW, I'M LOSING MY DAUGHTER TO SOME
8-YEAR-OLD KID.
SO, I'M FREAKING OUT. SO, NEXT DAY I'M
WALKING HER TO SCHOOL. Daddy-daughter
moment. She's holding my hand.
Then I just hear this, "Hi, Robbie." And
then everything goes slow motion. Just
boom.
And there he is. Little Robbie. This
stupid little Teenage Mutant Ninja
Turtle shirt. Cute kid, right?
Forget it. HE HAS THE AUDACITY TO LOOK
AT ME AND BE LIKE, "HI, MR. HARMESON."
I'M LIKE,
"ROBBIE."
RIGHT? THAT WAS IN MY HEAD, BY THE WAY.
THAT'D BE really creepy at an elementary
school.
So, this kid's messing me up. I I what
he looks like now. All right? I know
what he looks like, and I know his game.
All right? But I'm sitting at home. I'm
stewing about this all day long. My
daughter's at school. Finally, she comes
home all excited from school. And as she
gets in, SHE'S LIKE, "DADDY, DADDY,
DADDY, CAN I?" I'M LIKE, "YES, YES,
WHATEVER IT IS, YES, YOU CAN HAVE IT. I
LOVE YOU SO MUCH. JUST COME BACK TO ME.
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH." SHE'S LIKE,
"REALLY, DADDY?" SHE GETS ON MY LAP. SHE
KISSES ME ON the cheek. Any fathers know
that a daughter kiss you on the cheek,
it's over, right? She just melts me. She
gets off the lap. She goes in the other
room to tell my wife all excited. SHE'S
LIKE, "MOMMY, MOMMY, DADDY SAID YES. HE
SAID YES. ROBBIE CAN COME OVER." I'M
LIKE, "NO, ROBBIE."
DIRTY KID WON IN THE END.
He won.
>> Cuz uh every church now has a worship
leader. All right? And their job is to
lead the whole church in whatever song
they're singing. All right? So, you
know, you know, the whole church will be
rocking, you know, they're just like,
"Our God is an awesome God. He reigns."
And then the worship leader runs up, and
he says something I never expected to
hear in a church. You know, he runs up
there. He's like, "ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY,
LET'S LIFT YOUR VOICES AND LET'S MAKE
THE DEVIL REAL MAD WITH THIS NEXT
VERSE."
AND I'M LIKE, UM YEAH, I'd rather not.
So.
I'm like, yeah, the devil messes up a
lot of people's lives.
I'd rather the devil just continue not
knowing who I was.
DON'T WANT TO BE ON A FIRST NAME BASIS
with the devil. So.
Life is hard enough as it is
without being on the devil's hit list.
You see different stuff, man. You see
different stuff.
I'll tell you my favorite church people,
my favorite church people are the gospel
gangster rappers.
These are my favorite. Anybody ever seen
the gospel gangster rappers?
These are the people that just accepted
the Lord,
but can't quite let the streets go.
Still maybe participating in the
criminal activity on the weekends, you
know.
But I get it. I understand. It's a
process. It doesn't happen overnight,
you know.
Tell y'all the true story. I was down in
Atlanta. We were filming for this comedy
show. And once we got done filming, the
producer comes up to me and the rest of
the comedians and says, "Hey, if y'all
want to stick around, we're filming
we're filming a TV show
um
uh in the same studio. So, if y'all want
to stick around, you all can be in the
studio audience." So, they're like, "Oh,
you know, we're like, yeah, that's cool.
We'll do that." And so, the show we were
doing, it was it was like a gospel
version of American Idol. All right. So,
they would let everybody come through
and then and parade through and they
would send you whoever to Hollywood if
you were good enough, you know. And so,
so we got ready, you know. So, they were
there like we you know, we're sitting in
the audience and they're like, "Hey,
okay, let's send the first contestant
in." First contestant walks in.
And they're like, "Hey, how are you?
What are you going to do for us today?"
In walks the gospel gangster rapper.
All right. He walks in. He's like, "Hey,
don't worry about what I'm going to do.
All right."
Don't worry about what I'm going to do.
Okay, I'm about to bust this freestyle
for the Lord. Okay.
All right.
All right. Everybody put your L's up.
Put your L's up, okay?
Check it. Check it. Check it. Yo. Yo.
Yo. The Holy Spirit never could control
me. Only squeeze me and hold me. That's
what Jesus came and told me. Now, ain't
that bold, G? Now, the church where my
goals be cuz I'll be praying like I
supposed to be. Loving everybody who
comes CLOSE TO ME.
YEAH.
NOW, I WAS LIKE, Y'ALL WE WERE LIKE,
"OH, MAN, THAT'S GOOD. HE'S GOING to the
next round."
But the judges did not think the same
thing.
The judges took one look at him and they
were like, "That was good, but we don't
think you're quite right for this
competition."
Why did they tell him that?
He flipped the script on them, y'all. He
was like, "What? You disagree with me?
Don't get it twisted, fool. I'll still
the hammer back on the pistol, G.
That's how I got to see these
Seventh-day Adventists ain't as hard as
me. FOOL, WHAT? CHRIST SIDE. AMEN."
AMEN.
AND THE WHO THE JUDGES THEY WERE LIKE
AMEN security um
Scared us y'all scared me. I couldn't
even go to church next Sunday.
Yeah, couldn't go.
Had to stay home and watch church TV.
YEAH.
I LIKE CHURCH TV. CHURCH TV IS COOL, you
know. With church TV you get to pick
your own pastor, you know, I like that.
You know, you get freedom of religion in
your own home.
That's good. Now let me tell y'all
anytime I end up watching church TV, I
always end up watching the same person.
Y'all might have just seen him. His name
is Joel Osteen.
Y'all ever seen Joel Osteen?
Let me TELL YOU HEY, JOEL OSTEEN IS LIKE
THE happiest man on the planet.
You see him he comes out there Sunday
morning he's like, "Do you receive it
today?"
"I know you do."
"Hey, hey, don't let the devil STEAL
YOUR JOY."
HEY, I'M SITTING THERE LIKE, "OH, I FEEL
BETTER already Joel. This is great."
And the thing about Joel is Joel has a
story for every sermon that he gives.
Does not matter what he's preaching
about, he's going to break out into a
story.
You know, he'll be in the pulpit. He'll
be like, "You know, the other day
Victoria and I
we went to a village in the Philippines.
And when we got there, we saw this
little boy who only had one leg.
Just one.
So I preached life into that little boy.
And guess what? That other leg it just
popped right ON OUT. AMEN.
AMEN. I'M LIKE, "WHAT?"
I LIKE THAT IS A CHRISTMAS MIRACLE,
JOEL.